

# Den

# .NET Full Stack Developer

An ambitious and self-motivated software engineer with 4+ years of experience in development and 7 years in System Administration. Able to play a key role in website development to ensure maximum accessibility, user experience and usability. A quick learner who can absorb new ideas and communicate clearly and effectively.

## **SKILLS**

- BACK END: C#, ASP.NET Core, ASP.NET Web API, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET WebForms, ADO.NET, WC Workflow Foundation .NET Framew Identity Server 4, SignalR ORMs: EntityFramework, Dapper, Nhiberna Unity, Ninject, Autofac, ASP.NET Cc DI
- FRONT END: JavaScript, TypeScrip CSS, jQuery, AJAX, HTML/DHTML, Bootstrap, Angular, Vue.is, Knockor
- DESKTOP: WPF, WinForms DevExp
- PATTERNS AND PRACTICES REST, SOAP, CQRS, Event Sourcing, SOLI
- MUNIT TESTING NUnit, xUnit, MST-Coded UI, Moq, dotCover, Seleniur WebDriver

- CONTINUOUS INTEGRATION TFS, Jenkins, Azure DevOps
- DEV TOOLS, PROFILERS MS Visual Studio, MS SQL Management Studio, VS Code .NET Memory Profiler, dotTrace, Visual Studio Profiling Tools
- SOURCE CONTROL TOOLS TFS, Git, GitLab
- MOBILE TECHNOLOGIES Xamarin
- DATABASES MS SQL, SQLite, SQL CE, Azure SQL, SSRS, MongoDB, Cosmos DB
- SECURITY OWASP, OAuth, OpenID Connect, JWT
- METHODOLOGIES Agile, Scrum, Kanban

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Fintech/Payment System - Full Stack .Net Software Developer

APR 2021 - PRESENT

Description

A successful startup money transfer application created by 7 team members. I am working on new features, fixing bugs and making upgrades to existing parts. Assisting the designing and management of PostgreSQL database schemas and tables.

Used RESTful API's to connect and link Guest services to other API endpoints like membership and Registry.

I was also involved in Single Page Application using Angular and user dashboard using Angular material.



Tools & Technologies

C#.NET, ASP.NET MVC, ADO .Net, JavaScript, T-SQL, SQL Server, IIS

#### Healthcare App, eDev LLC - Full Stack .NET developer

MAR 2020 - APR 2021

Description

An enterprise-level system for registering patients in hospitals, monitoring their condition, and accounting medicines. The project was a legacy solution written in the company's internal framework using WebForms, jQuery, and KnockoutJS.

Team size: 8 team members

Responsibilities:

- Updated project modules and services to the new version of the framework.
- Conducted unit and integration tests.
- Fixed different kinds of bugs. Tools and technologies: WebForms, jQuery, Knockout.js.

Tools & Technologies

C#, ASP.NET, WebForms, jQuery, Knockout.js, HTML, JavaScript, CSS

#### Enterprise-Level App, AM-Integrator - .Net developer

JAN 2019 - MAR 2020

Description

It was a hardware-software project developed with the Microsoft .NET Framework platform and C/C++. The employee accounting system was created with the .NET stack including WinForms, ADO.NET and .NET Remoting. The streaming process in real-time with video cameras was implemented in C/C ++. I was mainly engaged in the development of the ASP .NET MVC 5 version of the project.

Team size: 15 team members

Responsibilities:

- Conducted unit and integration tests.
- Implemented insurance module.
- Optimized database queries, creating stored procedures and functions.
- Integrated external services.
- Updated different modules from desktop to web version using

ASP.NET MVC 5.

Tools & Technologies

Web Api, C#, WinForms, ADO.NET, .NET Remoting, C/C++, ASP.NET MVC 5, Entity Framework 6.

#### Media Player, AmconSoft - Full Stack .Net developer

MAY 2018 - JAN 2019

Description

The project was an add-on to the other multimedia player, which was

used for live video streaming. Team size: 4 team members

Responsibilities:



- Implemented a module for sequencer of the media player.
- Fixed different kinds of bugs related to UI and back-end side.
- Implemented desktop and web UI.

Tools & Technologies

ASP.NET Core, Entity Framework Core, WCF, WPF, Angular 9

Manufacturing Company - Technical Support Engineer, System Administrator

JUN 2011 - MAY 2018

Description

During this period, I set up and supported the company's websites

hosted on Windows Server. Team size: 20 team members

Responsibilities:

- Adjusted hardware and software for stable performance.
- Configured servers, fault-tolerant solutions, and infrastructure elements.
- Installed servers and services and modernized existing ones.
- Maintained office computer equipment.
- Wrote server software.
- Tested hardware.
- Set up workstations, networks, and network equipment including routers and modems.
- Was responsible for information security and user support.
- Organized backup and remote access.
- Procured new hardware and software.

Tools & Technologies

Wireshark, Microsoft Message Analyzer, PowerShell, RSAT, Sysinternals, PuTTy, IIS.

#### **EDUCATION**

Lviv Polytechnic National University, Faculty of Computer Science and Cybernetics

20011 - 2016

MS in Computer Science

## Languages

English - Intermediate

Ukrainian - Native

Russian - Fluent